Pennsylvania State University, Office of Physical Plant, Wastewater Treatment Plant records, 1909-2003 01228
Eberly Family Special Collections Library
Pennsylvania State University, Office of Physical Plant, Wastewater Treatment Plant records
1966-2016
Eberly Family Special Collections Library
01228
41.6 Linear Feet (40 containers)
Collection includes scientific reports prior to 1930, daily logs of the plant, discharge flow charts and erosion reports, annual reports from campuses, equipment files, and inspection reports.
Conditions Governing Access
This collection contains university records which are restricted for a period of 20 years from the date of their creation, in accordance with University Policies AD35 and AD95.
Biographical / Historical
Penn State owns and operates the Wastewater Treatment Plant (WWTP), and is permitted to treat up to 4 million gallons per day of wastewater. The plant is comprised of two treatment trains: activated sludge and trickling filters. The trickling filter processed water is sent through a Biological Nutrient Removal (BNR) process to reduce the nitrate levels in the wastewater. The disinfected treated water from these two parallel treatment trains is combined and spray irrigated on approximately 516 acres of farmland and forests near the University and helps to recharge the groundwater system.
Scope and Contents
Pennsylvania State University built the first wastewater treatment plant in 1913 to treat wastewater from the College and the Borough of State College, expanded several times after 1925, later dispersing effluvium to agricultural and forest land. The wastewater treatment plant is administered by the Utilities Division of the Office of Physical Plant.
Computer Assisted
- Abington Campus - Housing Feasibility study, utilities, 2013 (Box 38)
- Activated Sludge Plant Data, 1997 (Box 7)
- Activated Sludge Plant Operations, 1977 (Box 1)
- Agricultural Science and Industrial Facility - Erosion and Sediment Control Plan, 1993 (Box 6)
- Anaerobic Digester System, 1983 (Box 1)
- Architects/Engineers, 1994-1995 (Box 6)
- ASP Sludge Flow Chart, 1998 (Box 22)
- ASP Sludge Flow Chart, 1999 (Box 21)
- ASP Temperature, 1998 (Box 23)
- ASP Temperature, 2002 (Box 32)
  Conditions Governing Access note
  Restricted: Yes
- ASP Temperature, 2003 (Box 33)
- ASP Temperature Recording, 2000 (Box 25)
- ASP Temperature, 2001 (Box 30)
- Basis of Design Report by AECOM and Nittany Engineering, 2014 (Box 39)
- Basis of Design RFP, 2012 (Box 38)
- Beaver Stadium West Parking Lot - Erosion and Sediment Control Plan, 1997 (Box 6)
- Belt Filter Press, 1994-1995 (Box 15)
- Belt Filter Press, 1998 (Box 23)
- Belt Filter Press Report, 1996 (Box 12)
- Belt Filter Press, 1996-1997 (Box 7)
- Belt Filter Press Report, 2000 (Box 25)
- Belt Filter Press Report, 2000 (Box 26)
- Belt Filter Press Report, 2001 (Box 30)
- Belt Filter Press Report, 2002 (Box 32)
- Belt Filter Press Report, 2003 (Box 34)
- Berks Campus - Underground Utility Mapping Proposals, 2012 (Box 39)
- Big Hollow Chart, 1998 (Box 21)
- Big Hollow Chart, 1999 (Box 20)
- Big Hollow Chart, 2000 (Box 19)
- Big Hollow Dye Trace Testing Pilot Study Report, 2010 (Box 38)
- Biochemical Abstracts, 1909-1931 (Box 1)
- BOD-Lab Operations Worksheet, 2001 (Box 30)
- BOD-Lab Operations Worksheet, 2002 (Box 32)
- BOD-Lab Operations Worksheet, 2003 (Box 34)
- BOD Reports, 1996 (Box 7)
- BOD Work by Dr. Lindsey, 1928-1929 (Box 1)
- Bypass Sampling, 1997 (Box 12)
- CADD Generated Building Plans, 1994 (Box 6)
- Centralized Anaerobic Digester Evaluation, 2008 (Box 38)
- Centre County, Pennsylvania - Roadway Draining Report, 1998/04 (Box 6)
- CDM Water Treatment Feasibility Study, 2007-2010 (Box 18)
- Charts, 1998 (Box 21)
- Charts, 1999-2000 (Box 19)
- Charts/Graphs, 2000 (Box 25)
- Chester Engineering, 1993 (Box 6)
- Chlorinator Installation, 1964 (Box 1)
- Chlorinator Installation, 1978 (Box 1)
- Chlorinator System Building - Erosion and Sediment Control Plan, 1993 (Box 6)
- Chlorine Contract, 1996 (Box 7)
- Chlorine Contract, 1997 (Box 7)
- Chlorine Contract, 1998 (Box 24)
- Chlorine Residual Chart, 1994 (Box 16)
- Chlorine Residual Chart, 1995 (Box 17)
- Chlorine Residual Chart, 1996 (Box 12)
- Chlorine Residual Chart, 1997 (Box 13)
- Chlorine Residual Charts, 1998 (Box 23)
- Chlorine Residual Chart, 2001 (Box 30)
- Chlorine Residual Charts, 2002 (Box 32)
- Chlorine Residual Charts, 2003 (Box 33)
- Code Requirement Guidelines, 1987 (Box 6)
- Coliform Report, 2003 (Box 34)
- College Heights State College Borough Flow meeting, 2010-2012 (Box 38)
- College Township - Big Hollow Road Public Hearing, 1998 (Box 6)
- College Township Hospital Drive Row, 2011 (Box 39)
- College Village Channelization, 1991 (Box 6)
- Commonwealth Campuses - Subsurface Utility Engineering request for proposals, 2012 (Box 38)
- Convocation Events Center - Erosion and Sediment Control Plan, 1993 (Box 6)
- Correspondence, 1990-1996 (Box 4)
- Customer Service Report, 2000 (Box 26)
- Daily Digester, 1994-1995 (Box 15)
- Daily Digester, 1996 (Box 7)
- Daily Digester, 1998 (Box 23)
- Daily Digester Report, 1997 (Box 7)
- Daily Digester Report, 1997 (Box 14)
- Daily Digester Report, 2000 (Box 25)
- Daily Digester Report, 2001 (Box 30)
- Daily Digester Report, 2002 (Box 32)
- Daily Digester Report, 2003 (Box 34)
- Daily Log, 2002 (Box 32)
- Daily Log, 2003 (Box 33)
- Daily Log, 2000 (Box 25)
- Daily Log, 2001 (Box 26)
- Daily Meter Log, 2003 (Box 33)
- Daily Operational Report Pilgrim Sludge Press, 2000 (Box 26)
- Daily Operations Reports, 1995-1999 (Box 23)
- Daily Operational Report, 2000 (Box 25)
- Daily Operator's Data Log, 2002 (Box 31)
- Daily Plant Logs, 1994 (Box 16)
- Daily Plant Logs, 1995 (Box 17)
- Daily Plant Logs, 1996 (Box 12)
- Daily Plant Logs, 1996 (Box 13)
- Daily Plant Logs, 1997 (Box 13)
- Daily Reports, 1915/02-1931/01 (Box 2)
- Daily Reports, 1923-1930 (Box 2)
- Daily Reports, 1951/03-1957/06 (Box 2)
- Daily Reports, 1957/09-1964/05 (Box 2)
- DEP Annual Meetings, 2013-2014 (Box 38)
- Development of Policy SY 40 Disposal of Pollutants in University Sanitary Systems, 2011 (Box 38)
- DGS Inspector's Building Utilities, 1989 (Box 6)
- DRI Therm, Inc., 1992 (Box 6)
- Drought, 1997-1998 (Box 6)
- Effluent Discharge Force main shutoff valve installation project, 2010 (Box 38)
- Effluent Spray Pump House Logs, 1994 (Box 16)
- Effluent Spray Pump House Logs, 1995 (Box 18)
- Effluent Spray Pump House Logs, 1997 (Box 14)
- Effluent Spray Pump House Logs, 1998 (Box 23)
- Effluent Spray Pump House Logs, 2002 (Box 31)
- Effluent Sprayfield Lab Reports, 1993-1995 (Box 30)
- Effluent Sprayfield Lab Results, 1996-2001 (Box 29)
- Effluent Spray Pump House, 2001 (Box 30)
- Effluent Spray Pump House Logs, 1996 (Box 13)
- Effluent Spray Pump House Log, 2000 (Box 25)
- Effluent Spray Pump House Logs, 2003 (Box 33)
- Effluent Spray System, 1992-1993 (Box 35)
- Effluent Spray System Analysis Data, 1990 (Box 35)
- Effluent Spray System Analysis Data, 1991 (Box 35)
- Effluent Spray System Analysis Data, 1992 (Box 35)
- Effluent Spray System Analysis Data, 1993 (Box 35)
- Effluent Spray System Analysis Data, 1994 (Box 35)
- Effluent Spray System Analysis Data, 1995 (Box 35)
- Emergency Event Forms, 1991 (Box 4)
- Engineering Services Building Addition - Erosion and Sediment Control Plan, 1995 (Box 6)
- Engineering Services Rights of Way Checklist, 1997 (Box 6)
- Engineering Services Temporary Funding, 1996 (Box 6)
- Erosion and Sedimentation Control, 1993 (Box 6)
- Evaluation of Operating Performance, 1977 (Box 1)
- Evaluation of Wastewater and Residual Sludge, 1978 (Box 1)
- Fayette Campus - Wastewater System, 1966-2001 (Box 39)
- Field Worker Reports, 1994-1995 (Box 17)
- Field Worker Reports, 1996 (Box 12)
- Field Worker Report (Laterals), 1998 (Box 24)
- Field Worker Report (Laterals), 2000 (Box 26)
- Field Worker Report (Lateral), 2001 (Box 30)
- Field Worker Report (Laterals), 2002 (Box 31)
- Field Worker Report (Lateral), 2003 (Box 34)
- Fiscal Year, 2003-2005 (Box 31)
- Football Tailgating evaluation, 2016 (Box 38)
- Forecast of Loading Report, Forecast Period 2011-2015, 2010; Computer Assisted CD-ROMs
- Forecast Loading Report, 2003-2008 (Box 24)
- Forecast of Loading Report, 2006/03 (Box 24)
- Forecast of Loading Report, 2006 (Box 24)
- Forecast of Loading Report, 2007 (Box 24)
- Forecast of Loading Report, Forecast Period, 2010-2014; Computer Assisted CD-ROMs
- Forecast of Loading Report, 2015 (Box 18)
- Forecast of Loading Report - DVD, 2015 (Box 18)
- Forecast of Loading Report, 2016 (Box 18, Disk DVD)
- Forecast of Loading Report, 2017 (Box 40, Disk CD)
- Fox Hollow Chart, 1998 (Box 21)
- Fox Hollow Chart, 1999 (Box 20)
- Fox Hollow Chart, 2000 (Box 19)
- Gannett Fleming, Inc. Project #02-43010 Land Management Plan for Land Treatment, 2005-2009 (Box 18)
- Garfield Thomas Water Tunnel Drain to Sewer, 2004 (Box 38)
- General Information, 1989-1991 (Box 4)
- Golf Course Chart, 1998 (Box 21)
- Golf Course Chart, 1999 (Box 20)
- Golf Course Chart, 2000-2001 (Box 19)
- Golf Course Club House - Erosion and Sediment Control Plan, 1994 (Box 6)
- Groundwater Quality Assessment and Control Strategy for Wastewater Effluent Spray Facility Progress Report, 199410 (Box 18)
- H-ion Measurements, 1929-1931 (Box 1)
- HRB Modular Building Utilities Planning [near Barbara Building], 1993 (Box 5)
- Human Development - East Building Environmental System Manual, 1980-1996 (Box 4)
- IDHCA, 1990-1992 (Box 4)
- Innovation Park - Technology Center Research Park Sewer Rate Analysis, 2005-2008 (Box 39)
- Investigations in Foaming Control, 1977 (Box 1)
- Irrigation System-Lateral Valve Operation Schedule, 2000 (Box 26)
- Lab Operations - BOD, 1994 (Box 15)
- Lab Operations - BOD, 1997 (Box 7)
- Lab Operations - BOD, 1997 (Box 12)
- Lab Operations - BOD, 1998 (Box 24)
- Lab Operations - Solids, 1994-1995 (Box 15)
- Lab Operations - Solids, 1996-1997 (Box 7)
- Lab Operations - Solids, 1997 (Box 12)
- Lab Operations - Solids, 1998 (Box 24)
- Lab Operations - Solids BOD Report, 1995 (Box 16)
- Lab Operations - Solids, Stone Valley, 1997 (Box 7)
- Lab Operations - Stone Valley, 1995-1996 (Box 15)
- Lab Operations Worksheet - BOD, 1999-2000 (Box 26)
- Lab Operations Worksheet - Solids, 2000 (Box 26)
- Landfill, 1994-1995 (Box 15)
- Landfill, 1996-1997 (Box 7)
- Landfill, 1998 (Box 23)
- Landfill, 2002 (Box 31)
- Landfill Analysis, 2001 (Box 30)
- Landfill Manifests, 1994 (Box 16)
- Landfill Manifests, 1995 (Box 17)
- Landfill Manifests, 1996-1997 (Box 12)
- Landfill Manifest, 2001 (Box 30)
- Landfill Manifest, 2002 (Box 32)
- Langelier Index, 1994-1995 (Box 15)
- Langelier Index, 1996 (Box 7)
- Langelier Index, 1997 (Box 12)
- Langelier Index, 1997 (Box 15)
- Langelier Index, 1998 (Box 23)
- Lateral Data, Notebook, 1983-1995 (Box 8)
- Lateral Valve, 1994 (Box 16)
- Lateral Valve, 1997 (Box 14)
- Lateral Valve, 1998 (Box 23)
- Lateral Valve, 2001 (Box 26)
- Lateral Valve Operation Schedule, 2002 (Box 31)
- Lateral Valve, 2003 (Box 34)
- Leonhard Building - Erosion and Sediment Control Plan, 1993 (Box 6)
- Level Chart, 1998 (Box 22)
- Level Chart, 1998 (Box 21)
- Level Chart, 1999 (Box 21)
- Level/Press Chart, 2000 (Box 19)
- Living Filter Cost Avoidance Analysis, 2012 (Box 38)
- Manual for Land Application of Treated Sewage and Industrial Wastewater, undated (Box 39)
- Manual for Land Treatment of Wastewater, comments to DEP, 2009 (Box 39)
- Meta Phosphate, 1996 (Box 15)
- Meta-Phosphate, 1998 (Box 23)
- Meters/Chlorine Gas Feed Equipment Service Contracts, 1985-1993 (Box 18)
- Meters/Chlorine Gas Feed Equipment Service Contracts, 1994-1997 (Box 18)
- Meters/Chlorine Gas Feed Service Reports, 1998 (Box 23)
- Meters/Chlorine Gas Feed Service Reports, 2001 (Box 26)
- Meters/Chlorine Gas Feed Service Reports, 2002 (Box 32)
- Music Building II - Erosion and Sediment Control Plan, 1993 (Box 6)
- New Kensington Campus forecast report, 2018 (Box 40)
- Nitrate Operations Data, 1994-1995 (Box 15)
- Nitrate Operations Data, 1996-1997 (Box 7)
- Nitrif/Denitrif, 2001 (Box 26)
- Nitrif/Denitrif, 2002 (Box 31)
- Nitrif/Denitrif, 2003 (Box 33)
- Nitrification/Denitrification, 2000 (Box 25)
- Northcentral Regional Office Air Quality Program - Title V Operating Permit, 1999 (Box 39)
- Northcentral Regional Office Air Quality Program - Title V Operating Permit, 2006 (Box 39)
- Operation Logs, 1994 (Box 16)
- Operation Logs, 1995 (Box 17)
- Operation Logs, 1996-1997 (Box 12)
- Operator's Data Log, 1998 (Box 23)
- Operator's Data Log, 2000 (Box 25)
- Operator's Data Log, 2001 (Box 26)
- Operator's Data Log, 2002 (Box 31)
- Operator's Data Log, 2003 (Box 33)
- Orchard Road Chart, 1998 (Box 21)
- Orchard Road Chart, 1999 (Box 20)
- Orchard Road Chart, 2000 (Box 19)
- Pathological Incinerator Facility - Erosion and Sediment Control Plan, 1995 (Box 6)
- PAX Water Mixer manual, 2013 (Box 39)
- PCB Altoona, 1990 (Box 4)
- PCB Annual Report, 1986-1994 (Box 4)
- PCB Annual Report, 1991 (Box 6)
- PCB Capacitors, 1991 (Box 4)
- PCB Capital Annual Report, 1979-1987 (Box 4)
- PCB Citation, 1986 (Box 6)
- PCB General Information, 1987-1991 (Box 4)
- PCB Hershey Annual Report, 1979-1987 (Box 4)
- PCB Locations, 1985 (Box 4)
- PCB Mont Alto Annual Report, 1979-1987 (Box 4)
- PCB Ogontz, 1991 (Box 4)
- PCB Ogontz Annual Report, 1979-1987 (Box 4)
- PCB Priority List, Undated (Box 6)
- PCB Project, 1987 (Box 4)
- PCB Regulations, 1980 (Box 6)
- PCB Removals, 1988 (Box 4)
- PCB Reports, 1988-1991 (Box 4)
- PCB Retrofill, 1991/05/11 (Box 6)
- PCB Transformers Reports, 1986 (Box 6)
- PCB Transformers Status, 1990 (Box 6)
- PCB University Park Annual Report, 1979-1987 (Box 4)
- PCB Vendors, 1993 (Box 6)
- PCB York Annual Report, 1979-1987 (Box 4)
- PennDot Centre Region Metropolitan Planning Organization, 1998 (Box 6)
- PennDot Eastern Inner Loop Qualification Committee, 1998 (Box 6)
- PennDot Enhancement Guide, 1999 (Box 6)
- PennDot Intelligent Transportation System, 2001 (Box 6)
- PennDot Land Use Questionnaire, 2001 (Box 6)
- PennDot Permits - Bridge Occupancy Licenses, 1993 (Box 6)
- Pennsylvania State Gameland 176 Suitability Study, February 15, 1974 (Box 38)
- Ph Determinations, 1924-1932 (Box 1)
- Phosphate Test, 1995 (Box 15)
- Pilgrim Sludge Press, 2001 (Box 26)
- Plans and Drawings, Undated (Box 1)
- Plant Daily Log, 1998 (Box 23)
- Plant Daily Log, 1998 (Box 24)
- Playing Fields Project - Erosion and Sediment Control Plan, 1997 (Box 6)
- Potable Water Checklist, 1995-1996 (Box 14)
- Potable Water Daily Checklist, 1992-1994 (Box 14)
- Portable Water, Chlorine Monitoring Charts, 1996-1997 (Box 8)
- Portable Water, Chlorine, Monitoring Charts, 1996-1997 (Box 9)
- Portable Water, Chlorine, Monitoring Charts, 1996-1997 (Box 10)
- Portable Water, Chlorine, Monitoring Charts, 1996-1997 (Box 11)
- Potable Water Daily Checklist, 1996-1997 (Box 15)
- Press Chart, 1999-2000 (Box 20)
- Progress Reports, 1928-1933 (Box 1)
- Project - Act 537 Special Study final report, April 6, 2018 (Box 18)
- Quarterly Cost Reports, 1916-1931 (Box 1)
- Raw Sewage Flow, 1994 (Box 16)
- Raw Sewage Flow, 1995 (Box 17)
- Raw Sewage Flow, 1996 (Box 12)
- Raw Sewage Flow, 1997 (Box 13)
- Raw Sewage Flow, 2001 (Box 29)
- Raw Sewage Flow, 2002 (Box 32)
- Raw Sewage Flow, 2003 (Box 33)
- Raw Sewage Flow Charts, 1998 (Box 23)
- Reclaimed Water Distribution System Master Plan, 2006-2009 (Box 18)
- Reclaimed Water System RFP, 2013 (Box 38)
- Record of Sewage Flow, 1921-1922 (Box 2)
- Research Chart, 1999 (Box 20)
- Research Park Chart, 1998 (Box 21)
- Research Park Chart, 2000 (Box 19)
- Route 26 Stormwater Management, 1998/09 (Box 6)
- Routine Tests Record, 1924-1927 (Box 1)
- SANSM, 1995-1997 (Box 38, Disk Computer)
- Schuylkill Campus - Sewer System Inspection, 2009 (Box 39)
- Sewage Disposal Plant Log, 1926 (Box 2)
- Sewage Flow Meter Specification Sheets and Plans, Undated (Box 1)
- Sewage Plant Logs, 1917-1927 (Box 1)
- Sewage Treatment Plant Expansion, 1962 (Box 1)
- Sewage Treatment Plant Expansion Contract, 1962 (Box 1)
- Sewage Treatment Plant Expansion Legal Documents, 1962 (Box 1)
- Sewage Treatment Plant Log, 1963-1964/12 (Box 3)
- Sewage Treatment Plant Log, 1964/06-1965/03 (Box 3)
- Sewage Treatment Plant Log, 1965 (Box 3)
- Sewage Treatment Plant Log, 1967 (Box 3)
- Shaver's Creek Environmental Center Septic System Upgrades, 2015 (Box 39)
- Sludge Analysis, 1923 (Box 1)
- Sludge Analysis, 1931-1936 (Box 1)
- Sludge Filtration, 1935 (Box 1)
- Sludge Flow Chart, 2000 (Box 20)
- Sludge Flow Graphs, 2001-2003 (Box 27)
- Sludge Flow Graphs, 2001-2003 (Box 28)
- Sludge Press, 1998 (Box 23)
- Sludge Press, 2002 (Box 31)
- Sludge Press, 2003 (Box 33)
- Sludge Press Information, 1994 (Box 16)
- Sludge Press Information, 1995 (Box 17)
- Sludge Press Information, 1996 (Box 12)
- Sludge Press Information, 1997 (Box 14)
- Sludge Thickener Daily Log, 1998 (Box 23)
- Sludge Thickener Daily Log, 2000 (Box 25)
- Sludge Thickener Daily Log, 2003 (Box 33)
- Sludge Thickener Information, 1996-1997 (Box 14)
- Sludge Thickener Log, 2001 (Box 29)
- Sludge Thickener Daily Log, 2002 (Box 32)
- Sludge Thickener Information, 1994-1995 (Box 12)
- Solids - Lab Operations Worksheet, 2001 (Box 29)
- Solids - Lab Operations Worksheet, 2002 (Box 32)
- Solids - Lab Operations Worksheet, 2003 (Box 34)
- Soluble Phosphorus Removal, 1971 (Box 1)
- Specifications Sheets, 1976 (Box 1)
- Spray Field Suitability - Parizek (Box 37)
- Steam Line Improvement - Erosion and Sediment Control Plan, 1997 (Box 6)
- Test on Open and Closed Filters, 1915-1919 (Box 1)
- Test on Open and Closed Filters, 1920-1926 (Box 1)
- Troubleshooting Problem Article Reprints, 1980-1981 (Box 1)
- UAJA Big Hollow Pump Station Project, 2013 (Box 40)
- UAJA Spring Creek 316 (a) Study Final Report by Gannett Fleming, volume I, 1998 (Box 39)
- UAJA Spring Creek 316 (a) Study Final Report by Gannett Fleming - volume II, 1998 (Box 38)
- University Park Airport - Erosion and Sediment Control Plan, 1993 (Box 6)
- University Park - Digester Roof Replacement Project, 2008 (Box 39)
- University Park - Organic Load Investigation, 2011-2012 (Box 38)
- University Park - Organic Load Investigation Sampling Results, 2010 (Box 40)
- University Park - Sanitary Sewer Capacity Spreadsheet, 1994 (Box 40)
- University Park: Utilities Electrical Distribution PCB's, 1984-1994 (Box 4)
- University Park - Water and Sewer Rates, 2013 (Box 39)
- Upper Big Hollow Wastewater - discharge to sanitary sewer system, 2015 (Box 38)
- Utility Lab Report, 1994-1995 (Box 15)
- Utility Lab Report, 1997 (Box 15)
- Utility Relocation and Athletic Fields - Erosion and Sediment Control Plan, 1995 (Box 6)
- Wastewater Disposal Planning, 2011-2014 (Box 39)
- Wastewater Distribution Committee: Meeting Minutes, 1990-1998 (Box 4)
- Water Analyses: Chemical and Bacteriological, 1939-1947 (Box 1)
- Water Reuse Study, 2016 (Box 38)
- Water Services Landiak (Box 36)
- Water Supply System - Occupancy Certificate, 1993 (Box 6)
- Weekly Digester, 1994-1995 (Box 15)
- Weekly Digester, 1997 (Box 7)
- Weekly Digester Report, 1997 (Box 12)
- Weekly Digester Report, 1998 (Box 23)
- Weekly Digester Report, 2000 (Box 25)
- Weekly Digester Report, 2001 (Box 29)
- Weekly Digester Report, 2002 (Box 32)
- Weekly Digester Report, 2003 (Box 34)
- Well 33 Chart, 1998 (Box 21)
- Well 33 Chart, 1999-2000 (Box 19)
- Well 34 Chart, 1998 (Box 21)
- Well 34 Chart, 1999 (Box 19)
- Wellhead Protection Program - Steering Group, 2004 (Box 39)
- Wellhead Protection Program - Working Group, 2004 (Box 39)
- Whitehall Road Widening Project, 2011 (Box 38)
- Wright, R. E. Environmental, Inc., Undated (Box 5)